ABOLFAZL ABDALI

FRONT-END DEVELOEPR

CONTACT

https://abdalia.ir/
Abolfazlabdali0@gmail.com
https://www.linkedin.com/in/abolfazl-abdali/
https://github.com/abdalicodes
https://wa.me/989390623327

HARD SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Next.js, Redux, Apollo Client, React Query, Graph QL, Restful API, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, MUI, Post CSS, SASS, Chakra UI, Framer Motion

SOFT SKILLS

Creativity, Adaptability, Self-Motivation, Responsibility,

LANGUAGES

Persian: native English: A2 Turkish: native

EDUCATION

Undergraduate, Software Engineering 2016 – 2021

ABOUT ME

Self-taught and self-motivated Front-end developer with unlimited creativity, innovation and passion for designing and developing web applications. Worked as a WordPress developer for a long time. With more than 4 years of experience in web development and almost 2 years in React.

EXPERIENCE

Almas | May 2022 – July 2022 (3 months)

TypeScript – React.js – Next.js – Redux – Graph QL – SASS - Framer Motion In this project I've worked on Market-Place dashboard where sellers can add their products to the e-commerce platform.

I implement interactive UI features like Drag & Drop and image input for D3 images.

Freelance JavaScript Developer | Mar2021 – Apr 2022 (1 year 2 months)

 $\label{eq:html-css-JavaScript-TypeScript-React.} HTML-CSS-JavaScript-TypeScript-React.\\ js-Next.\\ js-Redux-Graph QL-Apollo Client-Git-React Query$

Worked on various projects in different concepts and scales and levelled up my skills.

WordPress Developer | Jan 2018 – Aug 2020 (2 year 8 months)

HTML - CSS - JavaScript

Build E-commerce websites with WordPress CMS and WooCommerce plugin. I Worked closely with the WordPress core API, e.g., built-in hooks.

PROJECTS

Crypto Landing: Code | Live

React - TypeScript - SASS - framer motion - Chakra UI - REST API

Portfolio: Code | Live

React – Next.js – TypeScript – Styled Components – Framer Motion

Music web app: Code | Live

React.js – MUI – React Query – Styled Components (I built this app based on Spotify redesign on Figma)

For further information about projects visit this page